[음악]
Uh Uh Too Spicy
You want my A to the Z
But you won't 無理に決まってる
当ててみて Sweet または Freak
What’s hiding underneath (I see)
躊躇うように探りを入れる君 チャンスはない Oh
Nah You won’t get it
No No, You won’t get it
I say
ぱっと一瞬で引き寄せる You'll be mine (Mine)
そっと近づいてきて Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
君を退屈にさせていた Every day
面白い罠を投げてあげるわ
飛び込んでみて
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
心に入り込む 君は
향신료 밑에 숨어 있는 것
I'm too Spicy
滲む刺激の中で君は
[음악]
ちょうどその瞬間
また違う私を発見する
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
나 자신
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Next step, Myself
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Too Spicy too too
Tell me what you see
[음악]
When you look at me
'Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
[음악]
勢いが違う Move
君を圧倒する Groove
[음악]
But you keep wasting your time Dude
Don't chase me 警告する 私は
[음악]
Erase me 遠くに逃げて
Hey もう分かる？
[음악]
元々 Bad I’m so bad honestly
So bad
全部私のものにする これからは Call you mine (Mine)
逃げるなら Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
いつもありきたりだった Every day
もう Ruleから外れるとき
難しくない
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
[음악]
心に入り込む 君は
레벨 2
I'm too Spicy
장치
[음악]
滲む刺激の中で君は
ちょうどその瞬間
また違う私を発見する
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Ready? Uh
[음악]
もう少し強度を上げて 次、次、次
독특한
One of a kind
[음악]
私たちは限界の先を行く Wow Wow Wow
That’s Right
매운 것
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
新しい挑戦の末に君は
[음악]
I'm too Spicy
変化する時間だよ 君は
[음악]
今この瞬間
また違う私を見つけ出す
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
무슨 일이야
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Next step, Myself
[음악]
I’m too Spicy I’m too Spicy
I’m too Spicy too too I’m too Spicy
[음악]
'Cause I
Oh Yeah
[음악]
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
(Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart)
ついに滲んでくる Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
[음악]
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
I’m too Spicy too too
[음악]
I’m too Spicy
For you
고마워요